&gt；&gt；steve kinney：除了。&gt；&gt；steve kinney：这会让你非常
&gt;&gt; Steve Kinney: Except.
&gt;&gt; Steve Kinney: That gets you to the very
首先呈现页面，然后我们的朋友出现并更改内容，对吧。
first page render, then our friend
comes along and changes stuff, right.
这会让你进入一个静态页面，
That'll get you to a static page,
如果你是一个内容网站，会让你走到那里的大部分路，对吧。
if you're a content site that will
get you most of the way there, right.
再一次，看到懒惰的Web性能方法，
Again, see the lazy approach
to web performance,
课程的新标题。
new title for the course.
很可能这并不是您最终渲染的唯一时间
So likely that is not the only time
that you are going to end up rendering
那一页，对。
the page, right.
并且大多数用户界面基于
And most user interfaced based
应用程序你经常移动东西，对吧。
applications you're moving
stuff around a lot, right.
这是那里正在发生的大多数事情。
This is the large majority
of what is happening there.
如果你用物体做奇怪的事情
And if you are doing weird
stuff with objects and
管理状态最终结果是您希望显示UI，对吧。
managing state the end result is
you wanna display a UI, right.
您希望基于所有其他JavaScript计算更改UI，这些计算
You want to change the UI based on all of
this other JavaScript calculation that
你在做什么。
you're doing.
因此，JavaScript可以做的影响渲染的事情的不完整列表
So an incomplete list of things that
JavaScript can do that impact rendering
性能是他们可以改变对象的类。
performance is they can change
the class of an object.
这是什么意思，班级2 x大小，对吧，它，
What does that mean,
does the class two x size, right, it,
它会改变它的尺寸吗，它会改变颜色吗？
does it change the dimensions of it,
does it change the color?
我们不知道这是怎么回事
We don't know what that does so
这意味着我们需要重新进行渲染过程的某些部分。
it means we need to do some part of
the rendering process all over again.
我们是否更改了对象的内联样式实际上与
Did we change the inline styles of
the objects is effectively the same as
改变班级，除了更黑暗。
the changing the class, except darker.
以及向页面添加或移除元素，
And adding or
removing elements to the page,
你可能需要重新布局页面，对吧。
you might need to re-lay out the page,
right.
这些都是可能发生的事情。
These are all things that can happen.
对于我们之前看到的所有步骤，好吧，DOM，
And for all the steps we saw before,
okay, the DOM,
CSS对象模型，渲染树，右边。
the CSS object model,
the render tree, right.
我们通常有效地保留DOM，有时还保留CSS对象模型。
We effectively mostly keep around the DOM
and sometimes the CSS object model.
如果您更改样式表，则必须重新计算。
If you change style sheets
that's gotta be recalculated.
但渲染树的其他所有内容都需要重新制作。
But everything else that render
tree needs to be remade.
当渲染树需要重新制作时，我们可能需要重新布局页面。
When the render tree needs to be remade
we probably need to re-layout the page.
当布局改变时，我们可能需要重新绘制页面，对吧。
When layout changes we probably
need to repaint the page, right.
因此，任何时候我们有这些大的影响，我们最终不得不重做很多这项工作。
So anytime we have these big effects we
end up having to redo a lot of this work.
所以这不是一次性的事情，而是很多次的事情。
So it's not a one-time thing,
it's a many times thing.
你可以做一些事情让你真正做到这一点。
And there are some things you
can do that really get you that.
还记得我们在介绍和介绍时沿着顶部的红色条吗？
Remember that red bar along the top
when we were in the introduction and
我们可以说你可以连接CPU？
we could say you could peg the CPU?
在这个过程中你可以做很多事情，因为他们都共享主要的
You can do a lot of stuff in this process
because they're all sharing the main
线程，对。
thread, right.
你的画，你的布局，你的JavaScript都在竞争
Your painting, your layout,
your JavaScript are all competing for
同样的电脑资源，对吧。
the same computer resources, right.
所以把这些都放在一起是很重要的。
So kinda keeping those all
together is important.
这就是渲染管道。
So this is the render pipeline.
JavaScript可以通过添加或来更改页面的样式
Javascript can change the styles
of a page by either adding or
删除类，这可能会更改页面的几何图形和布局。
removing classes, which could change
the geometry and the layout of the page.
可能会改变颜色。
That could change the colors.
就像，好的，当他们悬停时，我想把这个按钮从白色换成蓝色，对吧。
Like, okay, when they hover I wanna change
this button from white to blue, right.
需要你重新粉刷
That's gonna need you to repaint and
然后你需要将所有的新数据发送到GPU来完成，对吧，很酷。
then you need to send all that new data
over to the GPU to get done, right, cool.
所以这些步骤中的每一步都会触发一切改变风格，
So each one of those steps triggers
everything change the style,
更改计算样式所有重新计算都必须发生。
change the computed styles all
that recalculation has to happen.
任何可能改变的东西都可能改变几何形状，也可能没有改变几何形状
Anything could change that may or
may not have changed the geometry
那些东西现在不同了，发送到GPU，酷。
those things are now different,
send it to GPU, cool.
你不需要每次都做这些，对吧。
You don't always need to do all
of those every time, right.
如果您只是更改背景颜色或
In the event that you're just
changing the background color or
对象的不透明度，对。
the opacity of an object, right.
您需要重新布局页面吗？
Do you need to re-lay out the page?
可能不是，对吧。
Probably not, right.
所以有些时候，特别是像不透明度和CSS变换这样的东西，
So there are some times, especially with
stuff like opacity and CSS transforms,
在那里你甚至可以跳过油漆过程。
where you can actually skip
even the paint process.
你可以跳过这个的不同部分。
You can skip different parts of this.
如果窗口调整大小，则不会更改任何样式，因此
If the window resizes,
none of the styles have changed so
理论上你可以保留风格计算，对吧。
you can theoretically keep
the style calculations, right.
只是可能弹性框有不同的规则，您可能需要重新布局或
It's just maybe the flexbox has different
rules you might need to re-layout or
重新粉刷。
re-paint.
所以你并不总是需要做所有的事情，对吧。
So you don't always need
to do all of them, right.
有时候你可以跳过其中的一些，对吧。
Sometimes you can skip a few of them,
right.
这就是整个部分的内容，对吧。
And that's what this whole
section is about, right.
因为不做事，
Because not doing stuff,
跳过整个部分总是比做它们更快，对吧。
skipping entire sections will always
be faster than doing them, right.
同样的推论也适用，对吧，不做的事情比做的快
And the same corollary applies, right,
of not doing stuff is faster than doing
东西，做比你需要的多的东西也可能是有问题的，对吧。
stuff, doing stuff more than you need
to can also be problematic, right.
所以我们想跳过我们可以跳过的东西
So we want to skip
whatever we can skip and
我们绝对不想做任何超出我们需要的事情，对吧。
we definitely don't wanna do anything
more than we need to, right.
再一次，请参见懒惰方法对Web性能的影响，这是本课程的新标题。
Again, see the lazy approach to web
performance, new title for the course.